http://www.dairycare.com/pages/privacy-policy

EUR
We at DairyCare are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us.
DairyCare has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit DairyCare’s web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.
DairyCare strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, DairyCare intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred or retained.
COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIESSome of our web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about web site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the web site.
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our web site and your web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.
To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:
SECURITYWherever your Personal Information may be held within DairyCare or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the Personal Information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. All your ordering information — including your name, address, and credit card number — is encrypted using a secure server for maximum security.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, DairyCare web servers employ industry-standard methods to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on DairyCare’s servers are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
In the specific context of this security monitoring, there is no expectation of privacy. However, only in the case of actual law enforcement investigations, will we attempt to identify individual users or their usage habits.
ACCESS/ACCURACYTo the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, DairyCare wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on the web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting DairyCare should you need to update or correct that Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information toinfo@dairycare.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.
THIRD PARTY SERVICESThird parties may provide certain services available from DairybCare on DairyCare’s behalf. DairyCare may provide information, including Personal Information, that DairyCare collects on the web to third party service providers to help us deliver programs, products, information and services. DairyCare will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on DairyCare’sbehalf.
DairyCare does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on DairyCare’s behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against DairyCare’spolicy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent.
YOUR CONSENTBy using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to DairyCare’s processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above as well as those explained where DairyCare collects Personal Information on the web. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.
Your shopping cart is empty.
Subtotal
$ 0.00 USD
View Cart
Checkout
Sign up to have the latest news and member-only deals delivered straight to your inbox.
Sign Up NowFor Email Marketing you can trust.
Plainview Health Corp, manufacturer of DairyCare, Receives 2019 Best of West Long Branch Award!
Read more
November 17, 2019
Allergy and infections in newborns can be modified by probiotics, which shape HMO (complex human milk sugars) previously thought to be genetically determined, resulting in...
Read more
February 16, 2019
DairyCare™  Lactose Intolerance Digestive Supplement is the only single dose digestive supplement for Lactose Intolerance which provides consumers with sufficient lactase enzyme replacement for 24 hours, and without any side effects.
DairyCare is the only patented digestive supplement on the market that creates the lactase enzyme for 24 hours with just a single dose. Our product is also gluten & lactose-free with no GMO ingredients.
107 Monmouth Rd # 202West Long Branch, NJ, 07764 1-800-903-3222 CustomerService@DairyCare.com
Sign up to have the latest news and member-only deals delivered straight to your inbox.
Sign Up NowFor Email Marketing you can trust.
